presdo.com 2013-12-04

# Privacy Policy

Effective date: May 24, 2013

## 1\. Introduction

Presdo is committed to your privacy and the privacy of your information. This Privacy Policy applies to the information that users transmit to Presdo through the Presdo website at [match.presdo.com](http://match.presdo.com/) (the “Site”). This Privacy Policy informs you of what information Presdo collects from you on our Site and how Presdo uses that information. By using or accessing Presdo, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

## 2\. Information Collected by Presdo

When you register with Presdo, you provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, email address, photo, information about your contacts on social networks, and any other personal or preference information that you choose to provide to us. When you use Presdo, you may plan meetings and transmit information through various channels.

In addition, our Presdo Match product may also collect information about your profile, such as your current and past employment positions, educational history, and any event-specific information, including your stated interests, provided to us by you or event organizers.

We consider the above information your “Personally Identifiable Information”.

When you enter the Site, Presdo keeps track of which pages you click on. Presdo also collects your browser type and IP address. This information is collected for all Presdo visitors.

Presdo uses cookies and other standard web technology to collect information for its own use. A cookie is a small data file that the Site transfers to your computer hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Presdo uses session ID cookies to confirm that you are logged in. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature. However, refusing a cookie will hamper your navigation of our Site.

Presdo does not and will not, at any time, request Personally Identifiable Information in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication.

## 3\. Uses of the Collected Information

Presdo uses the information collected from you on its Site to:

  * authenticate your visits;
  * administer your account and customize the service we provide to you and other users;
  * enable you to share your information and communicate with other users;
  * make recommendations about users that may interest you and other users;
  * enable other users to find you through search or browsing;
  * help you connect to third-party services to exchange information such as contacts and calendar events;
  * contact you about announcements from Presdo or other users from time to time;
  * conduct research using the collected information to manage and improve our Site;
  * provide anonymous reporting for internal and external entities, including work with other vendors that help Presdo with data analysis, for example for product efficacy studies and market analysis

Presdo may enhance or merge Personally Identifiable Information with your other information and with data from third parties in order to better develop, market and provide our products, services and software. These third parties are all bound by this Privacy Policy and to not use the information for any purpose other than providing services to Presdo and to you under Presdo’s direction. Presdo stores Personally Identifiable Information in locations outside the direct control of Presdo (for instance, on servers co-located with hosting providers).

In addition, Presdo will not rent, sell, or share Personally Identifiable Information to any third parties for marketing purposes.

Presdo may periodically send you service-related announcements from time to time about the general operation of the service. Presdo reserves the right to send you such notices about your account even if you opt out of all voluntary email notifications.

When you update information, Presdo usually keeps a backup copy of the prior version for a reasonable period of time to enable reversion to the prior version of that information. Presdo also logs various types of information to help manage and improve the Site, in general and for you in particular. For example, Presdo identify items such as domains and browser types to understand how the Site is used and to report these statistics in the aggregate to the vendors that manage the technology of the Site.

Presdo limits access to personal information about users to employees who Presdo appropriately believes need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to users or in order to do their jobs. Presdo may share information collected through our websites with agents or contractors authorized solely to perform services on our behalf, such as providing support for our internal operations.

Presdo shall also disclose Personally Identifiable Information as permitted or required by law or as required by subpoena, search warrant, or other legal process. Presdo also shares information that it believes is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Presdo’s Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law.

As Presdo’s business evolves, Presdo may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including information provided by you, in connection with a merger, reorganization or sale of some or all of our assets or in the event of bankruptcy. In any such event, Personally Identifiable Information and other information may be one of the assets transferred. Presdo will post notice and seek your consent if that policy is materially different from this one before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

## 4\. How We Protect Your Information

Presdo uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. Presdo uses industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving data. We have security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from or about you.

We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Presdo or guarantee that your information on the Site may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. In the event that Personally Identifiable Information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, Presdo will promptly notify those users whose personal information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy or as otherwise required by applicable law.

## 5\. Spam Policy and Phishing

Presdo does not condone spamming. Do not abuse the Site by using them to spam, abuse, harass, or otherwise violate the Terms of Use or Privacy Policy.

## 6\. Controlling Your Personally Identifiable Information

Once you have shared your information with Presdo, you may still control how it is made available to others by taking the following the steps:

  * Review and modify your information – you can review the personal information you provided to us and make changes to the information about you that is shared with other users or to the settings for your account including your email and notification settings at any time. Much of this information is available for modification through the Site;
  * Contact us to modify your name and contact information associated with your account – some changes to your account, such as your name and contact information, require verification before they can be made. Contact us if you would like certain information which cannot be changed through the Site to be updated;
  * Contact us to deactivate your account – you may deactivate your account by contacting us. Once you deativate your account, your Personally Identifiable Information will no longer be visible to other users in the system. We may not retain your information and may delete any or all of your account information without liability. However, we may retain certain information contributed by you if we believe it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally identifiable data, account recovery, or if required by law.

## 7\. International Users; US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor

By visiting the Site and providing your data, you acknowledge and agree that due to the international dimension of Presdo, some of the data may be transmitted outside your resident jurisdiction. Furthermore, you acknowledge and agree that such data may be stored on servers in the United States.

Presdo complies with the EU and Swiss Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union and have also self-certified our privacy practices as consistent with US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor principles: Notice, Choice, Onward Transfer, Access and Accuracy, Security, Data Integrity and Enforcement. To view our certification, visit the [U.S. Department of Commerce’s Safe Harbor Web site](https://www.export.gov/safehrbr/list.aspx).

Presdo has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU AND SWISS SAFE HARBOR, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by Presdo, please visit the BBB EU AND SWISS SAFE HARBOR web site at [www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints](http://www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints) for more information and to file a complaint.

## 8\. Changes to the Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may be updated as Presdo’s services change and grow. Presdo will indicate any such changes on this page, by email, or through notice on our home page. Non-material changes and clarifications will take effect immediately, and material changes will take effect within 30 days of their posting on this site. If this Privacy Policy is changed, Presdo will post them and will indicate at the top of this page the policy’s new effective date. Presdo encourages you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. The most current version of the Privacy Policy can be found at http://match.presdo.com/privacy.

## 9\. Contact

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please first contact us at [privacy@presdo.com](mailto:privacy@presdo.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy). 

You may also contact us at:

**Presdo, Inc.**  
465 Fairchild Drive, Suite 128  
Mountain View, CA 94043  
United States of America  
Email: [privacy@presdo.com](mailto:privacy@presdo.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy)
